Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Deaccession files, 1944-2013; Series 16
  - Deaccessioned artworks alphabetical file, 1944-1989; Series 16 subseries 1
    - 3 Pairs of Curtains w/ Valances, 19th C., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 45)
    - Daubigny, Charles F. - A Hamlet on the Seine, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 46)
    - Daubigny, Charles F. - Rocky Precipice and Mountains, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 47)
    - David, Jacques Louis - Brutus, A Study, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 48)
    - David, Charles H. - Deepening Shadows, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 49)
    - Davis, Gene - Blueprint for Riveters, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 50)
    - Davis, Gene - Legato in Red, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 51)
    - Davis, Stuart - Cafe, Place des Vosges, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 52)
    - Davis, Warren - Notes on Copper, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 53)
    - De Block - A Dutch School, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 54)
    - Degas, Edgar - A Horse, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 55)
    - Delacroix, Ferdinand - An Arab Sky, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 56)
    - Delacroix - Landscape with Figures, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 57)
    - Deo, Marjoree - Fish, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 58)
    - Marjoree Deo - Watermelon, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 59)
    - Desgoffe, Blaise Alexandre - Souvenirs of the 16th and 17th Cent., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 60)
    - Dessar, Louis Paul - Landscape with Man and Sheep, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 61)
    - Detaille, Jean Baptiste Edouard - French Cuirassiers Bringing In Bavarian Prisoners, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 62)
    - Detaille - The Passing Regiment, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 63)
    - Detaille, Jean - General of the First Empire, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 64)
    - Dewey, Charles Melville - Edge of the Forest, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 65)
    - Diaz de la Pena, Narcisse Virgile - The Approaching Storm, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 66)
    - Diaz de la Pena, Marcisco - Broken Ground Near the Village, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 67)
    - Diaz de la Pena - Nymphs in Solitude, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 68)
    - Dodson, Sarah P.B. - Deborah, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 69)
    - Doolittle, Amos - Bonaparte in Trouble, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 70)
    - Downey, Juan - Against Shadows, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 71)
    - Downey, Juan - Do Your Own Concert, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 72)
    - Downey, Juan - The White Box, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 73)
    - Doughty, Thomas - Welsh Scenery (Landscape), undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 74)
    - Dubourg, M. - Views of the Remains of Ancient Buildings in Rome and its Vicinity (Book), undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 75)
    - Duchange, Gaspard - La Gallerie du Luxembourg..., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 76)
    - Dufy - La Reception, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 77)
    - Dupre, Jules - Moonlight by the Sea, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 78)
    - Dupre, Jules - Old Cottages Reflected in Water, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 79)
    - Dupre, Jules - The Pond of the Great Oak, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 80)
    - Dupre, Jules - Stormy Landscape, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 81)
    - Dupre, Jules - The Little Farm, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 82)
    - Duvieux, La Rochell - Plage D'Orient, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 83)
    - Eckout, E.J. - An Outdoor Concert, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 84)
    - (Workshop of El Greco - Saint Andrew, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 85)
    - Ellicott, Charles L. - Head of a Roman Girl (Unfinished), undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 86)
    - Epstein, Jacob - Italian Madonna, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Epstein, Jacob - Portrait of Ramsay MacDonald, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Escher, G. - Cathedral in Zurich, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Faed, John - Shakespeare & his Contemporaries, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Falguiere, Jean A.J. - Diana, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Falguiere, Jean A.J. - Female Nude, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Falguiere, Jean A.J. - Woman with Guitar, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Farley, Richard Blossom - Fog, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Fassett, Mrs. C. Adele - Vincenzo Vela, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Fassett, Mrs. Cornelia A. - Portrait of James C. Hall, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Foster, Ben - Late Autumn Moonrise, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Foster, Ben - The Lonely Road, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Frank, Jean Michel - 20th Cent. French Furniture, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - French, Daniel Chester - Death and the Sculptor, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Frere, C.T. - Village Street, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Frey, Johann Jakob - The Rome of the Popes, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Frey, Johann Jakob - Tivoli, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Fribel, C. - Swiss Mill Scene, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Frieske, Frederick Carl - Lady in Pink, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Gates, Robert - Kitty Hawk, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Gath, Ethel - Yellow and Blue, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Gauguin, Paul - Flowers in a Blue Vase, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Gericault, Jean A. - Study of a Torso, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Gerome, Jean Leon - Caesar Dead, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Giampetro, Alexander - Free Form, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Giampetro, Alexander - Stoneware Fruit Bowl, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Gifford, Sanford R. - The Catskills, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Glackens, W. - Illustration for a Story, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Gotthold, Florence Wolf - The DIfficult Task, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Goya, Francisco - Tauromachia, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Grabach, John R. - River Barges, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Grayson, Clifford P. - Mid - Day Dreams, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - Grabini, Sante - My Country Tis of Thee, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - Greaves, Walter - Portrait of J.A. McNeill Whistler, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - Greyer, J. - Flowers in a Glass Bowl, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 35)
    - Groll, Albert L. - The Land of the Hofri Indians, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 36)
    - Groll, Albert Lorey - Sunshower, Arizona, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 37)
    - Guarnerio, Pietro - Forced Prayer, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 38)
    - Guglielmi, O. Louis - Two Women, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 39)
    - Guillaume, L.M.D. - Carlisle, James M., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 40)
    - Haas, J.H.L. de - Holland Cattle, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 41)
    - Haden, Seymour - Etchings, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 42)
    - Hale, Lillian Westcott - Eleanor, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 43)
    - Hale, Lillian Westcott - Spring Reverie, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 44)
    - Hall, C.H. - The Dream, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 45)
    - Hamada, Shoji - Ho - 5 Vase, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 46)
    - Hamilton, John McLure - Sir Frederick Leighton, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 47)
    - Harris, Alexandrias Robertson - Snowberries, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 48)
    - Harrison, Birge - Rose and Silver - Moonrise, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 49)
    - Harrison, Thomas Alexander - Twilight, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 50)
    - Hart, James M. - Drove at the Ford, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 51)
    - Hawley, Margaret Foote - Portrait of Hildegarde Donaldson, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 52)
    - Hawthorne, Charles W. - A Fisherman's Wife, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 53)
    - Hayden, Charles H. - Silver Poplars - Cape Cod, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 54)
    - Hays, William J. - Head of a Bulldog, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 55)
    - Heilbirth, Ferdinand - Pincian Hill, Rome, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 56)
    - Heine, William - 9 Lithographic Prints, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 57)
    - Henner, Jean Jacques - Joan of Arc, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 58)
    - Henri, Robert - Willie Gee, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 59)
    - Herring, F.W. - William D. Kipack, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 60)
    - Hesloll - Winding Driveway, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 61)
    - Higgins, W. Victor - Apaches, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 62)
    - Hildebrandt, Cornelia Ellis - Portrait of Hannah Hildebrandt, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 63)
    - Hildebrandt, Edouard - Moonrise in Madeira, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 64)
    - Hirschl and Adler Galleries Inc., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 65)
    - Holmes, H. - High Up on the Blue Ridge, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 66)
    - Houser, Allan - Apache Buffalo Hunt/Apache Fire Dancer, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 67)
    - Howell, Felicie Waldo - A New England Street, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 68)
    - Huntington, Anna Hyatt - Africa - Water Hole, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 69)
    - Huntington, Daniel - Portraits of Mr. and Mrs. Taylor, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 70)
    - Huntington, Daniel - Kendall, Hon. Amos, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 71)
    - Huntington, Daniel - Kendall, Hon. Amos, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 72)
    - Hyde, Mary Margaret - A Relish, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 73)
    - Inman, John - Julia Strong, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 74)
    - Inman, Henry - George Washington in the Battle of Princeton, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 75)
    - Inness, George - Woods and Pasture, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 76)
    - Inness, George - Sunset, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 77)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Betta and Blotto, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 78)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Geraldine, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 79)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Madelaine, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 80)
    - Ireland, Beryl - A Nude, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 81)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Lillith, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 82)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Barbara by Firelight, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 83)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Girl in Black, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 84)
    - Ireland, Beryl - Animation, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 85)
    - Ireland, Beryl - A Lady with a Fan, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 86)
    - Ireland, Beryl - The Old Lady, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 87)
    - Isham, Samuel - Butterflies, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 88)
    - Israels, Jobef - Interior of a Cottage, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 89)
    - Jackson, John - Portrait, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 90)
    - Jacque, Charles - Duck Eating, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 91)
    - Jacque, Charles - Duck Preening, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 92)
    - Jacque, Charles - Duck Walking, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 93)
    - Jacque, Charles - Return to the Fold, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 94)
    - Jacque, Charles - Rooster, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 95)
    - Jacque, Charles - Rooster Eating, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 96)
    - Jacque, Charles - Standing Rooster, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 97)
    - Jamieson, Mitchell - The Family, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 98)
    - Japy, Louis Aime - Spring Landscape, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 99)
    - Japy, Louis Aime - Twilight, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 100)
    - Jeannin, G.C. - Vase of Flowers, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 101)
    - Jefferson, Joseph - Forest and Stream, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 102)
    - Johansen, John Christian - Portrait of the Artist's Family, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 103)
    - Johansen, John MacLane - Portrait, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 104)
    - Jones, Harry Leroy - Gray Day at North Trure, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 105)
    - Jones, H. Bolton - In November, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 106)
    - Jones, Hugh Bolton - Springtime, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 107)
    - Jonger, Alphonse - Portrait of William T. Evans, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 108)
    - Jaubert, Louis I. - Ruth Ray Maxwell, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 109)
    - Jourdain, J. - Cardinal Mercier Medal, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 110)
    - Kaemmerer, Frederich H. - Beach at Scheveningen..., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 111)
    - Kainen, Jacob - The Red Blouse, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 112)
    - Keith, Williams - Sunset, Marin County, California, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 113)
    - Keith, William - Portrait of Irving M. Scott, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 114)
    - Kemeys, Edward - Howling Coyote, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 115)
    - Kendall, William Sergeant - Narcissa, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 116)
    - Key, John Ross - Entrance to the Golden Gate, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 117)
    - Kisling, Philipp Heinrich - Portrait of Ursula Enderlin, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 118)
    - Kleinschmidt, Paul - The Cocktail, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 119)
    - Kleinschmidt, Paul - The Glove, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 120)
    - Kleinschmidt, Paul - Ice Cream Parlour, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 121)
    - Kleinschmidt, Paul - The Powder Puff, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 122)
    - Kleinschmidt, Paul - Study for Circus, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 123)
    - Kleinschmidt, Paul - At the Dressing Table, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 124)
    - Knaus, Ludwig - The Forester at Home, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 125)
    - Kuboto Photo Panels (Destroyed '99), undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 126)
    - M. Knoedler & Company, Inc., undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 127)
    - Lachenwitz, F. Siegmund - Dogs and Parrots, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 128)
    - Lafean, Richard C. - Stoneware Bowl, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 129)
    - Lambdin, James - John Cooper, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 130)
    - Lanman, Charles - A Home in the Woods, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 131)
    - Laszlo, Philip A. - Portrait of Mrs. Frank Kellogg, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 132)
    - Laszlo, Philip A. de - Portrait of Hon. Frank R. Kellogg, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 133)
    - Laslow, Philip A. de - Head of an Indian Prince, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 134)
    - Lazarus, Jacob H. - Portrait of Lafayette Foster, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 135)
    - Lawson, Robert - We Fix Flats, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 136)
    - Lazarus, Jacob H. - Odalisque, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 137)
    - Lee, Edna - Olive Green Flat Bowl, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 138)
    - Lely, Sir Peter - Portrait of a Lady, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 139)
    - Lenbach, Franz - Otto, Fuerst Von Bismar, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 140)
    - Leroff - Parlaghy, Princess - William Henry Bliss, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 141)
    - Le Roux, L. Eugene - ALexander II of Russia, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 142)
    - Leroux, Hector - Vestal Tuccia, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, John Chapman - Juggler, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - L'Hermitte, Leon Augustin - La Famille, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Linder, Franz - The Butterfly, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Linder, Franz - Woman in Black, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Lockwood, Wilton - Peonies, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Loir, Luigi - Effects of Snow, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Loiseau, Gustave - Flood, Environs of, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Lotz, Matilda - A Group of Dogs, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Loustaunau, Louis Aguste George - Monk Fishing, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Lumsden, Ernest - Theatre Street, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - McEntee, Jervis - Eastern Sky, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - MacEwen, Walter - An Ancestor, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - MacNeil, Herman A. - Medal, Hopi Prayer, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Maccari, Cesare - The Fortune Teller, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Madrazo, Frederico De - Dr. J.L.M. Curry, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Madrazo, R. De - Mrs. J.L. Coleman, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Marchette, Niccoli - Shakespeare, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Marche, Emile - Landscape with Cattle, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Marcke, Emile van - Cows in Meadow, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Marcke, Emile van - The Pasture, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Maril, Herman - The Dunes, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Marne - Jean Louis de - Interior, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Marne - Jean Louis de - Interior, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Martins, Maria - Nostalgia, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Marx, Gustave - Landscape, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Mathis, A. - Cathedral in Lausanne, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Matther, P. - Cathedral in Lucerne, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - Matther, P. - Street in Berne, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - McAdams, Alfred H. - Faraway, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - McFee, Henry Lee - The Window, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - McLaughlan, Donald Shaw - Pastorial, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - Matisse, Henri - Head of a Woman, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - Mehring, Howard - Black, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - Mehring, Howard - Untitled, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 35)
    - Melchers, Gari - The Sermon, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - Menpes, Mortimer - Venetian Balcony, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - Menpes, Mortimer - The Vista, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - Merrill, Katherine - The Warders, Charters, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - Meryon, Charles - L'Abside de Notre Dame, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 40)
    - Messer, Edmund C. - January, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 41)
    - Messer, Edmund C. - Sunset in London, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - Mettling, Louis - Study Head of a Young Man, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 43)
    - Meunier, Constantin - Woman of the People, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - Michel, Georges - Landscape, Twilight, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 45)
    - Muller, Charles Louis - Charlotte Corday in Prison, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - Miller, Richard E. - Torso, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 47)
    - Millet, Jean Francisque - Classical Landscape, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - Mills, Clark - Statuette of His Mother, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - Minor, Robert C. - Evidente, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo - Caryatid, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - Mongrin, Augustine - The Northwest Passage, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - Monticelli, Adolphe - Rocky Landscape, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 53)
    - Moretti, Antonio - Piazza of St. Peter's Rome, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 54)
    - Moretti, Antonio - Rome from the Forum, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 55)
    - Morghen, Raphael - Group Figure, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 56)
    - George Morland - The Warrener, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 57)
    - Morland, George - Landscape Cottage, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 58)
    - Moro, Antonio - Portrait, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 59)
    - Morot, Aime Nicholas - El Bravo Toro, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 60)
    - Moser, James Henry - In the Cornwall Hills, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 61)
    - Mosler, Henry - Girl Lying in a Field, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 62)
    - Mosler, Henry - Saving Grace, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 63)
    - Mosler, Henry - Dawn of Our Flag, undated; Series 16 subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 64)